Guide to the Sports Information Office Records, 1932-ongoing UA.13.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- UA2017-0067, 1927; 1937; 2015-2017
  - Field Hockey: Aisling Naughton, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Field Hockey: Meghan Norair, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Field Hockey: Chessie Ruffell, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Field Hockey: Savannah Story, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Field Hockey: Kelsey Wagner, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Swimming and Diving: Lee Christensen, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Swimming and Diving: Benedict Parfit, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Swimming and Diving: James Peek, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Swimming and Diving: Adriaan Venter, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Swimming and Diving, 2016-2017 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Volleyball, 2015 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Volleyball, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Volleyball: Laura Williams, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Volleyball: Cindy Marina, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Volleyball: Sasha Karelov, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Volleyball: Maggie Deichmeister, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Volleyball: Chloe DiPasquale, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Volleyball: Emily Sklar, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Volleyball: Jamie Stivers, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Volleyball: Jordan Tucker, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Volleyball: Alyse Whitaker, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Volleyball: Breanna Atkinson, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Volleyball: Christina Vucich, 2016 (Box 314 (UA2017-0067.5))
  - Baseball, 2016 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Baseball, 2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Duke Sports Hall of Fame Portraits & Headshots, 1927-2017; 1 items; CD (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - A Cut Above: 100 Seasons of Duke Basketball, 1927-2017; 1 items; DVD (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - FB Coach David Cutcliffe Bobby Dodd Coach of the Year Coin, 1927-2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Football: Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 1937 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Football: Photos, 1930s (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Football: Duke vs. NC State game program, 1927 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Baseball: Zeke Young, 2016-2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Baseball: Zack Kesterson, 2016-2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Baseball: Luke Glavin, 2016-2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Baseball: James Ziemba, 2016-2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Baseball: Jalen Phillips, 2016-2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Baseball: Cristian Perez, 2016-2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Baseball: Cameron Neal, 2016-2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Baseball: Kevin Lewallyn, 2016-2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Baseball: Nick Hendrix, 2016-2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Baseball: Evan Dougherty, 2016-2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Baseball: Thomas Crispi, 2016-2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Baseball: Bailey Clark, 2016-2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Baseball: Karl Blum, 2016-2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Baseball: Justin Bellinger, 2016-2017 (Box 315 (UA2017-0067.6))
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Liza Bragg, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Brittany Friese, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Jaimee Gundry, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Brittany Kahn, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Kirby Quinn, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Maddie Rusch, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Lindsay Schlichte, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Ashleigh Shanley, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Jessie Sutherland, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Women's Swimming and Diving: Colleen Wixted, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Men's Swimming and Diving: Rahul Chokshi, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Men's Swimming and Diving: Bradley Cline, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Men's Swimming and Diving: Kevin Fraser, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Men's Swimming and Diving: Marco Hosfeld, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Men's Swimming and Diving: Peter Kropp, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Men's Swimming and Diving: Joey Maginnis, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Men's Swimming and Diving: Michael Miller, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Men's Swimming and Diving: Emir Ozsuer, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Men's Swimming and Diving: Dylan Payne, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Men's Swimming and Diving: Parker Pearson, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Men's Swimming and Diving: Michael Seaberg, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Men's Swimming and Diving: Eric Strickland, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Men's Swimming and Diving: Kaz Takabayashi, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Bobak Shadpoor, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Alex Merriman, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Christopher Monti, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Ethan Yu, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Julia Lee, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Rita Somogyi, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Emmeline Yoo, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Alexandra Viqueria, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Wendi Oppenheim, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Tara Mullen-Boustiha, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Natalie Moszxzynski, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Samantha Meyers, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Libby Malcolm, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Cheng Ma, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Samantha Lee, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Angelica Hubbard, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Sarah Collins, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Isabella Barna, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Jacob Wiener, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Charles Copti, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Michael DeVito, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Eugene Chung, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Ted Cho, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Edward Chen, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Alexander Szilagyi, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Rod Shayesteh, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Fencing: Colin Colter, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Rowing, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Rowing: Tani O'Neill, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Rowing: Elizabeth Horne, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Rowing: Phoebe Donovan, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Women's Tennis, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Tennis: Chalena Scholl, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Tennis: Alyssa Smith, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Track and Field/Cross Country, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Track and Field: Madeline Kopp, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Track and Field: Michael Wilson, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Stephen Shine, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Dylan Murphy, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Track and Field: Ashton Huey, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Track and Field: Chaz Hawkins, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Track and Field: Connor Hall, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Daniel Moore, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Michal Filipczak, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Track and Field/Cross Country: Madison Granger, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Track and Field: Robert Rohner, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Track and Field: Daniel Golubovic, 2016-2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
  - Women's Lacrosse: Lars Kiel, 2017 (Box 316 (UA2017-0067.7))
- UA2018-0052, 1959-circa 2017
  - Duke Women's Golf Association Club Tournaments scrapbook, 1959-1985 (Box 317 (UA2018-0052.1))
  - Dick Groat letter and photocopy (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Slides and photographs of men's basketball, Women's field hockey, men's lacrosse, and football (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Football photo posters (Oversize-folder 3)
- UA2018-0069, 1944; 1957; 1986-2018
  This accession contains a large amount of material covering several decades and multiple sports, and includes clippings and other materials, as well as many individual player files the bulk dating 2016-2018.
  - John P. Wasielewski – Women's Volleyball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Cory Walton – Athletic Communications, Men's Basketball & Men's Golf, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Michelle Van Gorp – Women's Basketball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Casey Stevenson – Men's Basketball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Marc Spicijaric – Women's Tennis, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Rob Rowe – Blue Devil Network, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Brenna Rescigno – Field Hockey, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Christopher Pakes – Facilities & Special Events, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Alfred Morris – Baseball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Jesse Moore – Swimming & Diving, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Khary McGhee – Academics, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - David McClain – Women's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Jarred Martin – Field Hockey, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Jonathon Anderson – Baseball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Kevin Atkins – Ticketing, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Al Brown – Women's Basketball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Jeff Capel – Men's Basketball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Jeremy Anderson – Business Office, Game Operations, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Valerie Dahmen – Field Hockey, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Wesley Dameron – Athletic Facilities & Game Operations, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Michelle Dasso – Women's Tennis, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Ben DeLuca – Men's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Matthew Duncan – Ticket Office, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Lee Aldridge – Sports Information, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Niko Fantakis – Swimming & Diving, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Deidre Gordon – Athletic Development, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Ben Grafchik – Swimming & Diving, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Bob Harris – Men's Basketball & Men's Football Broadcasting, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Maureen Hasinger – Athletic Development, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Virginia Bane – Softball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Katie Hazelton – Swimming & Diving, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Marion Hobby – Football, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Jeff Ijjas – Iron Dukes, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Corey James – Sports Medicine, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Marcus Johnson – Football, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Amanda Chidester – Softball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Ian Haynes – IMG, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Kelsey Lyons – Blue Devil Network, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Emma Paradiso – Volleyball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Cadie Bates – Volleyball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Anna Kropf – Volleyball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Nicole Elattrache – Volleyball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Peter Zyla – Baseball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Luke Whitten – Baseball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Michael Smiciklas – Baseball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Mitch Stallings – Baseball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Al Pesto – Baseball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Max Miller – Baseball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - James McGhee – Baseball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Jack Labosky – Baseball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Zack Kone – Baseball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Jimmy Herron – Baseball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Ryan Day – Baseball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Ethan DeCaster – Baseball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Griffin Conine – Baseball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Daniel Calabretta – Baseball, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Nicolas Alvarez – Men's Tennis, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - 2017-18 – Men's Tennis, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Alexa Mackintire – Field Hockey, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Ashley Kristen – Field Hockey, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Kira-Lee Gmeiner – Field Hockey, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Ainsley Gill – Field Hockey, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Sarah Furey – Field Hockey, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Alyssa Chillano – Field Hockey, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - 2017 – Field Hockey, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Stephanie Pezzuti – Field Hockey, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Jessie Ambrose – Women's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Casey Black – Women's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Helen Cammerzell – Women's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Caitlin Carey – Women's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Quinlan Cullen – Women's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Sarah Frauen – Women's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Stuart Humphrey – Women's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Isabelle Montagne – Women's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Kitty Morrissey – Women's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Phoebe O'Hara – Women's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Devon Russell – Women's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Paige Russell – Women's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Maura Schwitter – Women's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Hayley Shaffer – Women's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - Gabrielle Thomas – Women's Lacrosse, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - 2018 Women's Lacrosse (Box UA2018-0069.1)
  - 1986-2008 Football Media Guides (Box UA2018-0069.2)
  - 2016 Football Media Guides (Box UA2018-0069.2)
  - 2016 Duke Athletics Hall of Fame Induction Program (Box UA2018-0069.2)
  - 2016 Duke Athletics Hall of Fame Induction Speeches DVD (Box UA2018-0069.2)
  - 2017 Duke Athletics Hall of Fame Football Game Program (Box UA2018-0069.2)
  - 2017 Duke Football Yearbook (Box UA2018-0069.2)
  - 1944 Duke Athletics P/E Staff Photo (Box UA2018-0069.2)
  - 1957 Duke Men's Basketball and Saudi Arabia King Saud Photo (Box UA2018-0069.2)
  - Miscellaneous Duke Football Pins and Buttons, 1986-2008 (Box UA2018-0069.2)
  - 2016 Football - Duke vs. N.C. Central (Box UA2018-0069.3)
  - 2016 Football - Duke vs. Wake Forest, Wake Forest (Box UA2018-0069.3)
  - 2016 Football - Duke vs. Northwestern, Northwestern (Box UA2018-0069.3)
  - 2016 Football - Duke vs. Notre Dame, Notre Dame (Box UA2018-0069.3)
  - 2016 Football - Duke vs. Virginia, Virginia (Box UA2018-0069.3)
  - 2016 Football - Duke vs. Army West Point, Army West Point (Box UA2018-0069.3)
  - 2016 Football - Duke vs. Georgia Tech (Box UA2018-0069.4)
  - 2016 Football - Duke vs. Louisville (Box UA2018-0069.4)
  - 2016 Football - Duke vs. Virginia Tech (Box UA2018-0069.4)
  - 2016 Football - Duke vs. North Carolina (Box UA2018-0069.4)
  - 2016 Football - Duke vs. Miami (Box UA2018-0069.4)
  - 2016 Football – Duke vs. Pittsburgh (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Shaun Wilson: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Taariq Shabazz: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Alonzo Saxton II: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Reno Rosene: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Norman "Mike" Ramsay: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Justin Perry: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Zach Muniz: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Trip McNeill: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Evan Lisle: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Wilson "Sterling" Korona: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - William Kline: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - William Holmquist: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Alex Gourley: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Bryon Fields: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Quaven Ferguson: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Colin Duffy: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Danny Doyle: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Austin Davis: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Qua'Shaun Chambers: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Zavier Carmichael: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Bronson Bruneau: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Gabriel Brandner: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Matt Bradley: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Parker Boehme: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Tinashe Bere: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Kane Banner: Football, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Cory Beck: Football staff member, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Drew Dudzik: Football staff member, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Josh Grizzard: Football staff member, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Jim Knowles: Football staff member, 2016 (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - 2017 Football Clips (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - 2017 Football Game-by-Game Box Scores (Box UA2018-0069.5)
  - Alec Ajnsztajn: Men's & Women's Fencing, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Pascual Di Tella: Men's & Women's Fencing, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Jared Garland: Men's & Women's Fencing, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Sam Goodman: Men's & Women's Fencing, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Dean Ischiropoulos: Men's & Women's Fencing, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Jan Maceczek: Men's & Women's Fencing, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Dakota Nollner: Men's & Women's Fencing, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Peter Yang: Men's & Women's Fencing, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Dara Buggay: Men's & Women's Fencing, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Sophie Caplin: Men's & Women's Fencing, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Haley Fisher: Men's & Women's Fencing, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Jennifer Ling: Men's & Women's Fencing, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Natalie Mosczcynski: Men's & Women's Fencing, 2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Samantha Harris: Women's Tennis, 2017-2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Rebecca Smaller: Women's Tennis, 2017-2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Abby Artmann: Rowing, 2017-2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Alexa Campbell: Rowing, 2017-2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Tara Christensen: Rowing, 2017-2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Jessica Findlay: Rowing, 2017-2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Sarah Fletcher: Rowing, 2017-2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Meagan Lew: Rowing, 2017-2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Katherine Maitland: Rowing, 2017-2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Taji Phillips: Rowing, 2017-2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Grace Williams: Rowing, 2017-2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - 2017-18 Swimming & Diving, 2017-2018 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Malinda Allen: Women's Soccer, 2017 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Schuyler DeBree: Women's Soccer, 2017 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Imani Dorsey: Women's Soccer, 2017 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Olivia Erlbeck: Women's Soccer, 2017 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Lexi Magliarditi: Women's Soccer, 2017 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Casey Martinez: Women's Soccer, 2017 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Ashton Miller: Women's Soccer, 2017 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Anna Munro: Women's Soccer, 2017 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - EJ Proctor: Women's Soccer, 2017 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Abby Pyne: Women's Soccer, 2017 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Rebecca Quinn: Women's Soccer, 2017 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Morgan Reid: Women's Soccer, 2017 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
  - Mary Love Taylor: Women's Soccer, 2017 (Box UA2018-0069.6)
- UA2019-0084, 2001; 2015-2019
  - Duke Football Media Guides, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.1)
  - Duke Football Yearbook, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.1)
  - Duke Chronicle Football Preview, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.1)
  - Duke Athletics Hall of Fame Induction Program, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.1)
  - Duke Athletics Hall of Fame Football Game Program, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.1)
  - Football Game-by-Game Files: Tulane, 2015 (Box UA2019-0084.1)
  - Football Game-by-Game Files: NC Central, 2015 (Box UA2019-0084.1)
  - Football Game-by-Game Files: NC Central, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.2)
  - Football Game-by-Game Files: Northwestern, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.2)
  - Football Game-by-Game Files: Baylor, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.2)
  - Football Game-by-Game Files: North Carolina, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.2)
  - Football Game-by-Game Files: Georgia Tech, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.3)
  - Football Game-by-Game Files: Wake Forest, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.3)
  - Football Game-by-Game Files: Northern Illinois, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.3)
  - Football: Media Guides, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.3)
  - Football Game-by-Game Files: Miami, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.4)
  - Football Game-by-Game Files: Virginia, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.4)
  - Football Game-by-Game Files: Florida State, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.4)
  - Football Game-by-Game Files: Pittsburgh, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.4)
  - Football Game-by-Game Files: Virginia Tech, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.4)
  - Football Game-by-Game Files: Army, 2017 (Box UA2019-0084.4)
  - Duke Football Clips, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Duke Football Year in Review, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Duke Football Lettermen, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Duke Football Snap Count, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Duke Football Banquet Program, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Duke Football Statistics Packet, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - GoDuke the Magazines, 2018 (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Clark Bulleit (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Jeremy McDuffie (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Terrell Lucas (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Johnathan Lloyd (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Trevon Lee (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Davis Koppenhaver (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Daniel Jones (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Jordan Hayes (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Daniel Helm (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Ben Humphreys (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Griffin Carter (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Matthew Clayton (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Matthew Eklund (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Brandon Feamster (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Keyston Fuller (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Kevin Gehsmanns (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Joe Giles-Harris (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Christian Harris (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Zach Harmon (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Twazanga Mugala (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Sayvon Sampson (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Collin Wareham (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Chris Taylor (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Zach Morris (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: Nicodem Pierre (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Player Bios: T.J. Rahming (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Staff Member Bios: Nathaniel Leonard (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Staff Member Bios: James Mitchell (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Staff Member Bios: Gerad Parker (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Football: Former Staff Member Bios: Cody Robinson (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Book: Cadets, Cannons and Legends The Football History of Morgan Park Military Academy (Box UA2019-0084.5)
  - Women's Volleyball: Fred Chao (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Sports Performance: Joshua Cooper (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Men's Basketball, Senior Administration: Mike Cragg (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Compliance: Mary Giardina (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Football, Senior Administration: Gerald Harrison (Box UA2019-0084.6)
  - Women's Basketball: Rene Haynes (Box UA2019-0084.6)